<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jeremy Forest</title>
    <link>https://jeremyforest.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jeremy Forest</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 03:18:38 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://jeremyforest.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://jeremyforest.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 03:18:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jeremyforest.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a bit of a jack of all trade. A neuroscientist by training, turned artificial neural network researcher and engineer, neuromorphics engineer and software developer. I love exploring new things !&#xA;I currently hold a postdoc position in the lab of Thomas Cleland at Cornell University oriented towards a computational neuroscience approach where we are working on the development of better olfactory processing models and the implementation of these models in neuromorphic architectured.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New theme</title>
      <link>https://jeremyforest.com/posts/2024_new_theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 01:56:52 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jeremyforest.com/posts/2024_new_theme/</guid>
      <description>Changed theme Just decided to update the website theme with this one. It look really nice ! Will also move some things around and complete other missing pieces here and there. See you around !</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coming Soon</title>
      <link>https://jeremyforest.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 01:26:51 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jeremyforest.com/projects/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dendrites as a biologically inspired approach to overcome catastrophic forgetting</title>
      <link>https://jeremyforest.com/posts/2023_continualai_unconference/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 01:56:52 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jeremyforest.com/posts/2023_continualai_unconference/</guid>
      <description>Presentation is available here&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m showing data and exemples of why dendrites can be a neat mechanisms for biologically inspired innovation to overcome catastrophic forgetting.&#xA;Abstract: Dendrites constitute a major unit element of biological neurons and more generally biological neural networks. Their multiple properties have mostly been ignored by the broader neuroscience and machine learning communities due to their lack of conceptual usefulness. So far, the theoretical framework of dendrites has been more or less that of summarizing the synaptic input activity to the soma.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
